Winter Castle is a tv movie, romance, comedy film directed by Marita Grabiak.
When Jenny attends her sister’s winter wedding at an ice hotel, her heart melts over the best man, the
problem is he unexpectedly brings a “plus one,” seemingly dashing her hopes for a wintery romance.
Jenny, played by Emilie Ullerup.
Craig, played by Kevin McGarry.
Lana, played by Meghan Heffern.
Sara, played by Habree Larratt.
Meg, played by Melanie Mullen.
Linda, played by Justine Eyre.
The Last Castle is a 2001 American action drama film directed by Rod Lurie, starring
Robert Redford, James Gandolfini, Mark Ruffalo, and Delroy Lindo.
The film portrays a struggle between inmates and the warden of a military prison,
based on the United States Disciplinary Barracks at Fort Leavenworth.
A highly decorated U.S.
Army Lieutenant General, court martialed and sentenced for insubordination, challenges
the prison commandant, a colonel, over his treatment of the prisoners.
After mobilizing the inmates, the former general leads an
uprising aiming to seize control of the prison.
The film was released in the United States on October 19, 2001.
It received mixed reviews from critics and was a financial disappointment,
grossing just $27 million against its $72 million budget.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.